[Evans] Let's define our procedure in the Python interpreter.
我们在 Python 解释器中定义我们的函数
We'll give it the name measure_udacity,
我们将它命名为 measure_udacity
and we'll give the parameter the name p.
并将参数命名为 p
Actually, we should probably give the parameter the name U, and we'll use an upper case U.
其实 我们也许该把参数命名为 U 而且是大写的 U
Not the most standard name for a parameter but appropriate in this case.
这虽不是最标准的参数名 但是在这里还是可以接受的
We'll introduce the variable count.
我们将引入变量 count (计数)
We'll set its initial value to 0.
我们把初始值设定为0
We're going to use count to keep track of the number of strings that we found
我们要使用 count 来追踪
that satisfy the udacity property.
所找到的符合 Udacity 属性字符串的个数
And we'll use the for-loop to go through all of the elements in U.
我们将使用 for 循环来遍历 U 中所有元素
Now we need to decide whether or not to count this element.
现在我们需要决定是否将这个元素计算在内
We can use an if statement to do this.
我们可以通过使用一个 if 语句来实现
We're going to need to use a comparison to check if the first character of the string
我们需要用一个比较来检查字符串的第一个字符
is an upper case U.
是否是大写的 U
If it is, we want to add 1 to the value of count.
如果是 我们就在 count 值上加1
If it's not, we do nothing.
如果不是 就什么都不做
So we use the equality test to check if the value at position 0 in e,
那么 我们用相等性判断来检查 e 中位置0的值
the current element of the list, is an upper case U.
检查列表中当前元素是否是大写的 U
If it is, we add 1 to count.
如果是 便加1
If not, we don't need to do anything, so we don't need an else clause.
如果不是 我们无需做任何事情 也就不需要一个 else 子句
And now we just need to return the value of count.
现在我们只需返回 count 值
Let's test our procedure.
现在测试我们的函数
Our first example, the input strings were Dave, Sebastian, and Katy.
我们的第一个例子 输入字符串为 Dave Sebastian 和 Katy
We see the result is 0, as expected.
我们看到 结果是0 不出所料
We'll try the second example where we have 2 strings that start with the letter U
我们再试试第二个例子 这里面有两个首字母为大写 U 的字符串
and see that we get the result 2 as the second value printed out.
我们看到打印出来的第二个值 即所得结果为2
We should also test a string that has a mix of Us and non-Us.
我们还应当测试首字母为大写 U 和首字母非大写 U 的字符串
Now we're passing in 4 strings.
现在我们传入四个字符串
They all start with a U, but only 2 of them start with an upper case U.
这些字符串都以 U 打头 但只有2个字符串首字母为大写 U
So the result for the third number printed out should also be a 2.
所以 结果即打印出来的第三个数字应当也为2
And we see that we get the expected result.
我们看见其得到了我们预想的结果